Subtitle Provide by dramacool.in Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.in [Admin.@YNG]
Xu Xin
شو شين
I was just about to talk to you.
لقد كنت على وشك التحدث معك.
Xu Xin, listen to me.
شو شين، استمع لي.
Xu Xin
شو شين
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Lu Ming
لو مينغ
Let him go.
دعوه يذهب.
Xu Xin
شو شين
Xu Xin, wake up.
شو شين، استيقظ.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
Xu Xin
شو شين
Yuan You
يوان يو
Where are we?
أين نحن؟
I don't know either.
انا أيضا لا اعرف.
When I woke up just now,
عندما استيقظت للتو،
I saw Lu Ming tying you up.
لقد رأيت لو مينغ يربطك.
I knocked him out while he wasn't looking.
لقد ضربته وهو لم يكن ينظر.
Is this the glass box you mentioned?
هل هذا هو الصندوق الزجاجي الذي ذكرته؟
Yes.
نعم.
That's the one.
هذا هو.
Xu Yuan was locked in here by Lu Ming.
تم حبس Xu Yuan هنا بواسطة Lu Ming.
And this control lever.
وهذا ذراع التحكم.
Lu Ming used this control lever
استخدم لو مينغ ذراع التحكم هذا
to make Xu Yuan disappear.
لجعل Xu Yuan يختفي.
Let's call the police right away.
دعونا نتصل بالشرطة على الفور.
It's useless, Xu Xin.
لا فائدة من ذلك ، شو شين.
You have to understand,
عليك أن تفهم،
whether it's Xiao Ya or Xu Yuan,
سواء كان شياو يا أو شو يوان،
no one in this world except you
لا أحد في هذا العالم سواك
remembers them anymore.
يتذكرهم بعد الآن.
So what should we do now?
إذن ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل الآن؟
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Let me think.
دعني أفكر.
Let me do it.
دعني افعل ذلك.
Yuan You.
يوان يو.
Xu Xin.
شو شين.
Now it's time for him to face the consequences.
والآن حان الوقت لمواجهة العواقب.
We just need to push this control lever down,
كل ما نحتاجه هو الضغط على ذراع التحكم هذا للأسفل،
and you'll be free from him forever.
وسوف تكون حرا منه إلى الأبد.
Yuan You.
يوان يو.
This isn't something you should do.
هذا ليس شيئا يجب عليك فعله.
You've already done enough for me.
لقد فعلت ما يكفي بالنسبة لي.
No.
لا.
Xu Xin.
شو شين.
Xu Xin, don't.
شو شين، لا تفعل ذلك.
No.
لا.
No, Xu Xin.
لا، شو شين.
Please, no, Xu Xin.
من فضلك، لا، شو شين.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
I'm not feeling well today, I can't come.
أنا لا أشعر بأنني على ما يرام اليوم، لا أستطيع الحضور.
Can you cover for me today?
هل يمكنك أن تغطيني اليوم؟
What do you mean by slacking off, bro?
ماذا تقصد بالتراخي يا أخي؟
Last time you weren't feeling well,
في المرة الأخيرة التي لم تكن تشعر فيها أنك على ما يرام،
I covered for you the whole day.
لقد غطيتك طوال اليوم.
It's settled then.
لقد تم تسويتها بعد ذلك.
I'm hanging up.
أنا أعلق.
Please, I'm begging you.
من فضلك، أنا أتوسل إليك.
I don't want to die.
لا أريد أن أموت.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
You'll soon go to a new place.
سوف تذهب إلى مكان جديد قريبا.
A very, very good place.
مكان جيد جدًا جدًا.
I don't want to die.
لا أريد أن أموت.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
You won't die.
لن تموت.
You're just going somewhere else.
أنت فقط تذهب إلى مكان آخر.
It's a rebirth of the soul.
إنها ولادة جديدة للروح.
No one will suffer because of this.
لن يعاني أحد بسبب هذا.
And no one will remember you.
ولن يتذكرك أحد .
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
All of this is
كل هذا
a gift from above to me.
هدية من السماء لي.
You're about to go to a better place.
أنت على وشك الذهاب إلى مكان أفضل.
And I'll keep all my memories of you
وسأحتفظ بكل ذكرياتي عنك
here with me.
هنا معي.
I once thought
لقد اعتقدت ذات مرة
my life would always be like this.
حياتي ستكون دائما مثل هذا.
Whether it was the old me or who I am now,
سواء كان ذلك أنا القديم أو ما أنا عليه الآن،
except for this secret only I know,
باستثناء هذا السر الذي أعرفه وحدي،
I was just wasting my days away.
لقد كنت أضيع أيامي فقط.
Until
حتى
the day you appeared.
اليوم الذي ظهرت فيه.
Your smile was as warm as sunshine.
كانت ابتسامتك دافئة مثل أشعة الشمس.
I wanted to know you.
أردت أن أعرفك.
I wanted to know everything about you.
أردت أن أعرف كل شيء عنك.
I learned your name.
لقد علمت اسمك.
Xu Xin.
شو شين.
It's such a beautiful name.
إنه اسم جميل جدًا.
You like reading.
أنت تحب القراءة.
You love literature.
أنت تحب الأدب.
Do you like flowers?
هل تحب الزهور؟
I think you would.
أعتقد أنك ستفعل.
Little Tangyuan.
تانغيوان الصغير.
Look.
ينظر.
This is the sea.
هذا هو البحر.
This is the beach.
هذا هو الشاطئ.
This is the sun.
هذه هي الشمس.
Let's go to the beach together someday, okay?
دعنا نذهب إلى الشاطئ معًا يومًا ما، حسنًا؟
You must be tired.
لابد أنك متعب.
Have some water.
خذ بعض الماء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I didn't realize taking care of kids every day was so exhausting.
لم أكن أدرك أن رعاية الأطفال كل يوم أمر مرهق للغاية.
You all really work hard.
أنتم جميعا تعملون بجد حقا.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
We're used to it.
لقد اعتدنا على ذلك.
Since Little Tangyuan came here,
منذ أن جاء ليتل تانغ يوان إلى هنا،
you're the one he's closest to.
أنت الشخص الأقرب إليه.
I don't know why,
أنا لا أعرف لماذا،
but I also feel close to him when I see him.
ولكنني أشعر أيضًا بالقرب منه عندما أراه.
Even though he can't express his feelings,
على الرغم من أنه لا يستطيع التعبير عن مشاعره،
I can still feel a lot from him.
لا أزال أشعر بالكثير منه.
He really likes you.
إنه يحبك حقا.
I wonder
انا اتعجب
if he thinks of you as his mom.
إذا كان يعتبرك أمه.
I wish I could have a child like him.
أتمنى أن يكون لدي طفل مثله.
Miss Xu.
السيدة شو.
You...
أنت...
I have to go back.
يجب علي أن أعود.
My husband is here to pick me up.
زوجي هنا ليأخذني.
Okay.
تمام.
Little Tangyuan.
تانغيوان الصغير.
I'll give this back to you for now.
سأعيد لك هذا في الوقت الحالي.
Bye-bye.
وداعا وداعا.
But we can't be together.
ولكننا لا نستطيع أن نكون معاً.
Because you have a husband.
لأن لديك زوجًا.
That troublesome Lu Ming.
هذا لو مينغ المزعج.
I could tell right away
يمكنني أن أقول ذلك على الفور
you two aren't happy together.
أنتم لستما سعداء معًا.
What happened
ماذا حدث
was a chance given to me by fate.
كانت فرصة منحت لي من قبل القدر.
Xu Xin.
شو شين.
Luckily, you weren't seriously hurt in the accident.
لحسن الحظ، لم تصب بأذى خطير في الحادث.
But you lost all your memories of me.
لكنك فقدت كل ذكرياتك معي.
Yet fate still tied us together.
لكن القدر لا زال يربطنا ببعضنا البعض.
That night,
في تلك الليلة،
I intended to get rid of Chen Fei.
لقد كنت أقصد التخلص من تشين فيي.
But your arrival stopped me.
ولكن وصولك أوقفني.
I know
أنا أعرف
that night, you didn't want to
في تلك الليلة، لم تكن تريد ذلك
leave with that man.
إذهب مع هذا الرجل.
Because we are the ones meant to be together.
لأننا من المفترض أن نكون معًا.
Xu Xin
شو شين
For you,
لك،
I can do anything.
أنا أستطيع أن أفعل أي شيء.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I need to plant a seed in your heart.
أريد أن أزرع بذرة في قلبك.
A seed that can help you
بذرة يمكن أن تساعدك
awaken in this terrible marriage.
استيقظوا في هذا الزواج الرهيب.
Be patient.
كن صبوراً.
Xu Xin,
شو شين,
I will save you.
سأنقذك.
I'll make use of everything I have.
سأستغل كل ما أملك.
Sorry about that.
آسف على ذلك.
Children are a good cover.
الأطفال غطاء جيد.
But
لكن
they can also cause unexpected trouble.
كما أنها قد تسبب مشاكل غير متوقعة.
The door is locked.
الباب مغلق.
I guided Little Tangyuan
لقد قمت بإرشاد ليتل تانغ يوان
to draw a picture of the crime scene.
لرسم صورة لمسرح الجريمة.
It will bring us together again.
إنه سيجمعنا معًا مرة أخرى.
One day, I'll share my secrets with you.
يوما ما، سأشارك أسرارى معك.
About this machine.
حول هذه الآلة.
About everything about me.
عن كل شيء عني.
But not now.
ولكن ليس الآن.
The rift between you is growing wider.
الخلاف بينكم يتسع أكثر.
And that's exactly what I need.
وهذا بالضبط ما أحتاجه.
If you want to be reborn,
إذا كنت تريد أن تولد من جديد،
you must go through rebirth through nirvana.
يجب عليك أن تمر بالولادة الجديدة من خلال النيرفانا.
Xu Yuan, sis.
شو يوان، أختي.
Xu Yuan, sis, save me.
شو يوان، أختي، أنقذيني.
Sis.
أخت.
Sis, help me.
أختي ساعديني.
Xu Yuan.
شو يوان.
You can only rely on me now.
لا يمكنك الاعتماد علي الآن.
Don't let me see you here again.
لا تدعني أراك هنا مرة أخرى.
Go.
يذهب.
You really did come to me.
لقد أتيت إلي حقا.
Everything went so smoothly.
كل شيء سار بسلاسة.
Even Chen Fei, the unpredictable one,
حتى تشين فاي، الشخص الذي لا يمكن التنبؤ به،
became our catalyst.
أصبح حافزنا.
She's mentally and intellectually healthy.
إنها تتمتع بصحة عقلية وفكرية جيدة.
Give me some time.
أعطني بعض الوقت.
I believe she'll regain her mental health.
أعتقد أنها ستستعيد صحتها العقلية.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
I can use my knowledge to help them.
أستطيع استخدام معرفتي لمساعدتهم.
I find it very meaningful.
أجده ذا معنى كبير.
It's also why I studied psychology.
وهذا هو السبب أيضًا الذي جعلني أدرس علم النفس.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Want some candy?
هل تريد بعض الحلوى؟
You want candy, huh?
هل تريد الحلوى؟
Let uncle take you to get some, okay?
دع عمك يأخذك للحصول على بعض، حسنًا؟
Wait for me a moment.
انتظرني لحظة.
The candy's outside.
الحلوى بالخارج.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Divorce.
الطلاق.
Just as I suspected.
كما توقعت.
That man has been lying to you all along.
لقد كان هذا الرجل يكذب عليك طوال الوقت.
I'll get you
سأحصل عليك
out of this toxic marriage.
من هذا الزواج السام.
This is the happiest time of my life.
هذا هو أسعد وقت في حياتي.
Our hearts have never been this close.
لم تكن قلوبنا قريبة هكذا من قبل.
Xu Xin,
شو شين,
I love you.
أحبك.
I'm the only one you can rely on now.
أنا الشخص الوحيد الذي يمكنك الاعتماد عليه الآن.
Just a little more.
فقط قليلا أكثر.
I want to expose that person's ugliness
أريد أن أفضح قبح هذا الشخص
completely in front of you.
أمامك بالكامل.
Xu Xin
شو شين
Xu Xin, listen to me.
شو شين، استمع لي.
Let him go.
دعوه يذهب.
Xu Xin
شو شين
Don't.
لا.
If you don't push it down,
إذا لم تضغط عليه للأسفل،
Lu Ming won't let you go.
لو مينغ لن يسمح لك بالذهاب.
Think about Xiao Ya.
فكر في شياو يا.
And your sister.
وأختك.
And the girl in red.
والفتاة باللون الأحمر.
Little Tangyuan drew a girl.
رسم تانغ يوان الصغير فتاة.
They can't die in vain.
لا يمكن أن يموتوا عبثا.
Someone has to stand up for them.
يجب على شخص ما أن يدافع عنهم.
Xu Xin
شو شين
Don't, Xu Xin.
لا تفعل ذلك، شو شين.
Don't.
لا.
I don't think I've ever told you.
لا أعتقد أنني أخبرتك من قبل.
That girl was wearing red, right?
كانت تلك الفتاة ترتدي اللون الأحمر، أليس كذلك؟
You told me.
لقد اخبرتني.
No.
لا.
I never told you.
لم أخبرك أبدا.
You definitely told me.
لقد قلت لي بالتأكيد.
You forgot, Xu Xin.
لقد نسيت ، شو شين.
I'm sure I never told you.
أنا متأكد من أنني لم أخبرك أبدًا.
And also,
وأيضا،
Lu Ming
لو مينغ
Why is his mouth gagged?
لماذا فمه مكمما؟
He's been lying to you all along.
لقد كان يكذب عليك طوال الوقت.
Do you still want to listen to his nonsense?
هل لا تزال تريد الاستماع إلى هراءه؟
Wait, Yuan You.
انتظر، يوان يو.
We all need to calm down right now.
نحن جميعا بحاجة إلى الهدوء الآن.
Lu Ming can't fight back anymore.
لم يعد بإمكان لو مينغ القتال بعد الآن.
What we need to do now
ما نحتاج إلى القيام به الآن
is find someone to help us.
هو العثور على شخص لمساعدتنا.
Someone will definitely help us.
بالتأكيد سوف يساعدنا شخص ما.
Xu Xin
شو شين
No one will believe us anymore.
لن يصدقنا أحد بعد الآن
If you don't do it,
إذا لم تفعل ذلك،
I'll decide for you.
سأقرر لك.
Yuan You
يوان يو
If...
لو...
If Lu Ming really killed them,
إذا كان لو مينغ قد قتلهم حقًا،
I don't want you to become like him.
لا أريدك أن تصبح مثله.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Don't do this.
لا تفعل هذا.
Xu Xin
شو شين
One day you'll thank me.
سوف تشكرني يوما ما.
Yuan You
يوان يو
Let go.
اتركه.
Why are you treating me like this?
لماذا تعاملني هكذا؟
I've done so much for you.
لقد فعلت الكثير من أجلك.
Why don't you trust me?
لماذا لا تثق بي؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Let go.
اتركه.
Let her go.
اسمح لها أن تذهب.
Xu Xin
شو شين
I believe everyone here
أنا أصدق الجميع هنا
from childhood to now,
من الطفولة إلى الآن،
whether from books,
سواء من الكتب،
the stage, or the big screen,
المسرح أو الشاشة الكبيرة
have all encountered
لقد واجهوا جميعا
many classic masterpieces.
العديد من الروائع الكلاسيكية.
And there are many different opinions.
وهناك آراء كثيرة مختلفة.
So, who would like to share?
إذن من يرغب بالمشاركة؟
I'm sure everyone's tired of hearing
أنا متأكد من أن الجميع سئموا من سماع
Xu Xin's opinions.
آراء Xu Xin.
Let's hear from someone else.
دعونا نسمع من شخص آخر.
This student.
هذا الطالب.
I remember your name is Lu Ming, right?
أتذكر أن اسمك هو لو مينغ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.